Ngu Brice Che

Minneapolis, Minnesota, United States

ngubriceche@outlook.com

(763) 347-9057

linkedin.com/in/supbrice

Summary

Diligent and hardworking Cloud Engineer with over 4 years of experience with Azure Cloud Platform and other cloud computing services. Expertise in deploying cloud infrastructure, as well as developing cloud-based applications, testing, evaluating, solving issues, performing inspections, and ensuring the continuous integration process of cloud resources. I am a team player and have excellent communication skills.

Experience



www Workforce Management Analyst

WTW

Aug 2022 - Present (4 months +)

- Providing recommendations for improved performance within the Workforce Management team and for supported workgroups.
- Responsible for generating quarterly workforce projections based on upcoming production needs.
- · Created monthly reports for a management team that compared workforce costs to actual revenue production.
- Involved in several workforce allocation research projects designed at assisting in budgeting for planned corporate growth.

RapidScale Cloud Engineer

RapidScale

Mar 2021 - Aug 2022 (1 year 6 months)

- Azure load balancing Solutions, including Layer 7 application gateway and layer 4 load balancer.
- Managing Virtual Networks and subnets.
- · Creating and managing Network Security Groups for Virtual machines and Virtual Networks for security purposes. • Configuration and troubleshooting of VPN connections such as Site to site, Point to Site (Including point-to-site connections using ADD authentication), Vnet-to-Vnet and Vet Peering.
- Creation and administration of Route tables to manage traffic within Azure environments.
- Integration of Web applications with Virtual networks to ensure communication with Vets and On-Premise side.
- Mentor for new colleagues to ensure quality deliver and case handling.

式 IT Support Specialist

Comm-Works (Acquired by New Era Technology 2022)

Sep 2016 - Feb 2021 (4 years 6 months)

- Installed, managed, and maintained all IT-related systems, including hardware, software, database, networks, and video conferencing.
- Provided first-level technical support to end users on proprietary software and applications, including installation, basic usage, and appropriate service level to warranty.
- Performed troubleshooting techniques over the phone or via web messenger to identify and resolve issues.
- · Established patterns for reoccurring issues and provided input to development teams



Customer Service Representative/Data Entry

Bio-Techne

Jun 2012 - Aug 2016 (4 years 3 months)

- Discussed account details with customers and recommended products and services to them based on listening to their needs and interests.
- Solved problems with billing, service, or product quality issues customers called about by making referrals to the appropriate supervisor, investigating billing details, or scheduling service appointments.
- Achieved high call quality scores each week, based on each customer's level of satisfaction after they received a resolution.

Education

Paul's Computer Institute

Course Completion in CCNA Routing and Switching, Computer Systems Networking and Telecommunications

Oct 2016 - Jan 2017

St. RIta's Technical and Commercial School

GED, Computer Science Aug 2011 - Jun 2012

Skills

Workforce Management • SQL • Salesforce.com • Microsoft Excel • Virtual Private Network (VPN) • Azure Resource Manager • Load Balancing • Service-Level Agreements (SLA) • Cloud Management • Data Migration